http://www.johndaly.com/privacy-policy/

HEART OF A LION
Loading... Please wait...
Security
John Daly recognizes the need for a secure shopping site to protect you, our valued guest. Therefore, our servers use 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, and this is verified independently by Verisign. This is the highest encryption level currently available, so you can feel safe and secure when placing your order with JohnDaly.com!
PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR JOHNDALY.COM
JohnDaly.com recognizes the importance of your privacy and protecting your personal information while you are visiting our web site. It is our goal to provide our customers with the opportunity to access and use our products and services in a secure environment. When you supply us with personal information, we make a commitment to you that the information will be used for internal use only and no information will be sold, rented or loaned to any third party. This includes contact information like your name and e-mail address, financial information like your credit card number and demographic information such as your address.
WE RECOGNIZE YOUR EXPECTATION OF PRIVACY
We understand that you expect us to maintain proper safeguards to protect your confidential information, and we recognize the need for security in the protection of your privacy. Thus, we have established policies and procedures to prevent misuse of your information. Please see our Security Policy link for further explanations of our security measures.
WE COLLECT, USE AND TREAT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU ONLY FOR LEGITIMATE BUSINESS PURPOSES
We gather, use and keep information about you only if required by law, or we believe that the information is necessary to administer our business, and/or to serve your interests by providing you with products, services, and other opportunities. Your information is processed through secured servers certified as such by Verisign (an independent Internet security company).
WE MAINTAIN ACCURATE INFORMATION
We have procedures in place for maintaining and updating information about our customers in accordance with commercial standards.WE HAVE POLICIES AND PROCEDURES LIMITING EMPLOYEE ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We maintain procedures and security levels to limit employee access to your personally identifiable information to those employees with a business reason for knowing such information. Our employees are trained on customer confidentiality and privacy. We take appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce employee privacy responsibilities.WE MAINTAIN SECRUITY PROCEDURES TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We maintain appropriate security standards and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. We periodically upgrade and test these security procedures and safeguards.WE RESTRICT THE DISCLOSURE OF ACCOUNT INFORMATION
JohnDaly.com does not reveal specific information about you or your account(s) or other personally identifiable data outside of JohnDaly.com unless (1) the information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you; (2) you request it; (3) the disclosure is required or allowed by law; or (4) you have been informed about the possibility of such disclosures for marketing or similar purposes and we have given you the opportunity to decline.
WE MAINTAIN YOUR PRIVACY IN BUSINESS RELATIONSHIPS WITH THIRD PARTIES
We do not sell Personal Information to third parties. However, sometimes it is necessary to provide your personably identifiable information to third parties such as vendors or service companies that we hire to assist us in the preparation and handling of your account.
Shop
John Daly Store
Return/Refund Policy
About John
Bio
Schedule
Fan Club
Drink
Sign Up for Daly Deals!
Name
Email
© 2020 John Daly. All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy | Terms of Use | Sitemap
6701 College Drive - Suite 150 - Suffolk - VA - 23435
Site Design and Development by IntuitSolutions
